Nayab Shafaqat

+92306 5871554 nayabm21@gmail.com Lahore, Pakistan

EXECUTIVE SUMMARY

To commence a successful career by hardworking and implementing skills in highly competitive organization where I can dispense my knowledge in some appropriate direction to get experience and to explore more opportunities. Highly self-motivated individual with fast-learning ability and independent problem-solving skills.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Ranop Solution Pvt Ltd

01/2018 - 05/2018

Report Writer/Post Processor

- 3G/4G reporting using Map Info
 - o RSCP Level, EcNo, PSC, Pillot Pollution, Throughput
- Log files analysis
 - Coverage Analysis

To ensure the logical serving of the cells.

Overshooting Analysis

To ensure the quality of signals.

DCR Analysis

Poor coverage, pilot pollution and Overshooting.

HOSR Analysis

Incoming HOs, Outgoing HOs.

- Customer Complaints handling
 - Locate the customer location on mapinfo by given coordinates

To ensure the logical coverage.

To ensure there is no issue of multiserver and no dominancy.

• Coordination with the DT Engrs.

UET, Lahore

09/2017 - 12/2017

Internee

- Studied subnetting, VLANs and Protocols (STP, VTP, OSPF)
- Complaints Handling
 - Physical layer is working properly

To ensure there is no cut down in fiber.

Data Link layer is working properly

To ensure the switches go through correct mac addresses.

Network layer is working properly

To ensure the IP configuration is correct.

Configured Routes and managed Paper Work.

Education

Bachelor of Engineering –Telecommunication, University of Engineering and Technology, Taxila 2013 – 2017

Final Year Prject

Gain Enhanced Multilayer Antenna 06/2017 – 07/2017

This antenna is designed to operate at 2.5GHz and 5.9GHz with the gain of 13dB and 9dB, which are used for WLAN communication and vehicle to vehicle communication respectively. Performance of this antenna is achieved by cutting different slots from patches. Upper patch having U and E slots while lower patch having HUT shape in the structure. Wider bandwidths with the high gains are achieved with this design.

Tool: High Frequency Structural Simulator

Strengths and SKILLS

- Teamwork
- Multi-tasking
- Time Management
- Good communication
- Environment Adaptive

- TEMS Investigation
- Map info
- Cacti
- SecureCRT 8.1
- Cisco Packet Tracer

Refrences

Will be furnished upon request.